They're gonna need more men.
Blacklight is a action, thriller, adventure film directed by Mark Williams.
Travis Block is a shadowy Government agent who specializes in
removing operatives whose covers have been exposed.
He then has to uncover a deadly conspiracy within his own
ranks that reaches the highest echelons of power.
Travis Block, played by Liam Neeson.
Mira Jones, played by Emmy Raver-Lampman.
Dusty Crane, played by Taylor John Smith.
Gabriel Robinson, played by Aidan Quinn.
Drew Hawthorne, played by Tim Draxl.
Amanda Block, played by Claire van der Boom.
Blacklight is a 2022 action thriller film directed
and co-written by Mark Williams.
The film stars Liam Neeson as a brooding FBI fixer who becomes involved in a government
conspiracy; Emmy Raver-Lampman, Taylor John Smith, and Aidan Quinn also star.
Blacklight was released in the United States on February
11, 2022, by Briarcliff Entertainment.
It struggled both commercially and critically.
With a production budget of $43 million, it only grossed about $16
million worldwide, making it a box-office bomb.
It received overwhelmingly negative reviews from critics, with some
calling it one of Liam Neeson's worst performances and movies.
The storyline, action sequences, and overall direction were widely criticized,
adding to its reputation as a low point in Neeson's career.
The film explores themes of undercover agent,
hitman, blackmail, fbi, conspiracy.
The tone is emotional and intense.